

## Arman Ajabkhani

Senior Software Engineer

#### **PROFILE**

A a Senior Software Engineer with experience in building high-performing, scalable, enterprisegrade applications.

Communicative, ability to collaborate well within and with other teams.

With Process Oriented personality, and strong focus on quality being able to understand and apply Unit Tests, Clean Code and Design Patterns.

Interested in learning new concepts, technical challenges, large scale distributed systems, also working with cloud-based systems covering infrastructure, platform and software as services.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science** from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

## **LANGUAGES**

English(intermediate)

Persian(native)

Germany(elementary)

#### **CONTACT**

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Github: Arman's profile

Resume Source: LaTeX graphical resume

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Snapp (Smart Transportation System)

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

July 2019 - Present

- Designing and Developing new generation of Financial micro-services.
- Migrating Finincial Services to Microservices from Monolithic(PHP).
- Providing services with high volumes of concurrent transactions(Java & Golang).
- Developing services with SpringBoot, Spring Cloud, MySql, Docker and Redis.
- Implementing CI/CD using Gitlab and OpenShift.

## Sava Arman Kish (Crypto-Currency Exchange)

## Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

- Monitoring all phases of development process and analysis, design, testing, and implementation
- Developing reactive services using Java, Spring, OpenApi, RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Designing, development and maintaining Exchange and Notification micro-services.

#### TOSAN (Financial and Payment Solution)

#### Senior Software Engineer / Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

Java developer in Channel Manager Team:

- Developing functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization module.
- Developing and Maintaining Exchange and Corporate Banking subsystems.
- Make technical design decisions on exchange subsystem with little supervision.
- Developing and implementing RMI and Web Services (REST / SOAP).
- Works on improvements in development toolset including testing frameworks, deployment scripts and monitoring libraries.

#### Team lead in Channel Manager team:

- Mentoring, coaching, training, and planning tasks for technical team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment & Maintenance several applications & micro-services.
- Ensuring code quality and following best software development practices Unit Tests, Code Reviews.

## Elm o Sanat (Time Attendance System)

## C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

C#/ASP.NET developer in School product Team:

- Implementing several new features and maintain the School application.
- Designing and Developing a customized report generator.
- Implementing a replication using SQL Server and SOAP web service.



# Arman Ajabkhani

Senior Software Engineer

## **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**

| Programming Language          | Desinging Architecture                        |
|-------------------------------|---|
| Java                          | Micro-services                                |
| Golang (Learning)             | Software Architecture Patterns                |
| C# / ASP.NET                  | Test Driven Development                       |
| Javascript / HTML / CSS       | Event Driven Architecture                     |
| Spring                        | Domain Driven Development                     |
| Spring                        | RESTful Services                              |
| Spring Boot                   | Design Patterns                               |
| Spring MVC                    | Live Migration                                |
| Spring Security               | Concurrent Programming                        |
| Spring Cloud                  | Reactive Programming                          |
| Spring Batch                  | Buillding / Deployment / Testing              |
| Spring Data / JPA / Hibernate | Jenkins/Gitlab CI/CD                          |
| Spring AOP / aspectj          | Git / Subversion / TFS                        |
| DataBases / Message Brokers / | Docker / OpenShift                            |
| Oracle                        | Gradle / Maven                                |
| MySQL / SQL Server            | JUnit / TestNg / Mockito                      |
| Redis / Ehcache               | Methodology / Documenting / Domain            |
| ELK                           | Scrum / Kanban                                |
| ActiveMQ / RabbitMQ           | Jira / TFS / HP ALM                           |
| Vert.x / RxJava               | Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting         |
| Swagger                       | Financial / Payment / Crypto Currency Systems |